A Guide to the Deeds of easement of the Virginia Dept. of Historic Resources, 1969-2010
Library of Virginia
- Oregon Hill Historic District - 617 S. Cherry St., Richmond City (Acc. 41222), 2002 (Box 5)
- Oregon Hill Historic District - 716 Holly St., Richmond City (Acc. 45157), 1992 (Box 5)
- Oregon Hill Historic District - 117 S. Laurel St., Richmond City (Acc. 45157), 1992 (Box 5)
- Oregon Hill Historic District - 128 S. Laurel St., Richmond City (Acc. 37305), 1998 (Box 5)
- Oregon Hill Historic District - 402 S. Laurel St., Richmond City (Acc. 42473), 2005 (Box 5)
- Oregon Hill Historic District - 608 S. Laurel St., Richmond City (Acc. 42473), 2004 (Box 5)
- Oregon Hill Historic District - 610 S. Laurel St., Richmond City (Acc. 42473), 2004 (Box 5)
- Oregon Hill Historic District - 314 S. Pine St., Richmond City (Acc. 37305), 1999 (Box 5)
- Oregon Hill Historic District - 413 S. Pine St., Richmond City (Acc. 35680), 1996 (Box 5)
- Oregon Hill Historic District - 521 and 523 S. Pine St., Richmond City (Acc. 37305), 1998 (Box 5)
- Oregon Hill Historic District - 522 S. Pine St., Richmond City (Acc. 41222), 2003 (Box 5)
- Oregon Hill Historic District - 605 S. Pine St., Richmond City (Acc. 45157), 1992 (Box 5)
- Oregon Hill Historic District - 612 S. Spring St., Richmond City (Acc. 45157), 1992 (Box 5)
- Oregon Hill Historic District - 711 S. Spring St., Richmond City (Acc. 35680), 1997 (Box 5)
- Oregon Hill Historic District - 808 S. Spring St., Richmond City (Acc. 35680), 1996 (Box 5)
- Oregon Hill Historic District - 810 S. Spring St., Richmond City (Acc. 35680), 1996 (Box 5)
- Oregon Hill Historic District - 818 S. Spring St., Richmond City (Acc. 45157), 1993 (Box 5)
- Oregon Hill Historic District - Jacob House - 619 W. Cary St., Richmond City (Acc. 41222), 2003 (Box 5)
- Oregon Hill Historic District - Smith House - 611 W. Cary St., Richmond City (Acc. 41222), 2003 (Box 5)
- Price House - 208-212 W. Franklin St., Richmond City (Acc. 29886), 1977 (Box 5)
- Palace Theater, Northampton County (Acc. 44477), 2007 Oct 4 (Box 9)
- Palmyra Lock and Mill Site - Fluvanna County Courthouse Historic District, Fluvanna County (Acc. 41222 and 42473), 2001, 2003 (Box 5)
- Pamplin Pipe Factory, Appomattox County (Acc. 45052), 2009 July 14 (Box 10)
- Paramount Theater, Charlottesville (Acc. 39119), 2001 (Box 5)
- Parsons House (Samuel Parsons House, Oregon Hill), Richmond City (Acc. 39119), 2000 (Box 5)
- Paxton, Powhatan County (Acc. 39119, 1989 (Box 5)
- Paxton House - Glen Maury, Buena Vista (Acc. 39119), 2001 (Box 5)
- Pembroke Manor, Virginia Beach (Acc. 45157), 1987 (Box 5)
- Phoenix Bank, Suffolk (Acc. 43430), 2006 (Box 5)
- Pilgrim's Rest, Fauquier County and Prince William County (Acc. 45052), 2008 Dec 29 (Box 10)
- Pilgrim's Rest, Prince William County (Acc. 35188 and 43430), 1994, 2006 (Box 5)
- Pine Knot, Albemarle County (Acc. 35680), 1997 (Box 5)
- Pine Slash, Hanover County (Acc. 32920), 1986 (Box 5)
- Planters National Bank Building, Fredericksburg (Acc. 43430), 2006 (Box 5)
- Pleasant Hill, Virginia Beach (Acc. 29886), 1973 (Box 5)
- Pleasant Point, Surry County (Acc. 37305), 1998 (Box 5)
- Plumb House, Waynesboro (Acc. 39119), 2001 (Box 5)
- Poor House Farm - Barrier Islands Center, Northampton County (Acc. 41222), 2002 (Box 5)
- Powell-Ablard House, Alexandria (Acc. 45157), 1986 (Box 5)
- Powell-McMullen House, Greene County (Acc. 41222), 2002 (Box 5)
- Prentis House, Suffolk (Acc. 44477), 2007 Nov 27 (Box 9)
- Preston House, Salem (Acc. 43430), 2006 (Box 5)
- Prestwould, Mecklenburg County (Acc. 39119), 2000 (Box 5)
- Prospect Hill, Botetourt County (Acc. 30973), 1980 (Box 5)
- Pulaski Theater, Pulaski County (Acc. 39119), 2001 (Box 5)
- Pythian Castle, Portsmouth (Acc. 37305), 1999 (Box 5)
- Race Mills, Opequon Historic District, Frederick County (Acc. 45052), 2009 Sep 1 (Box 5)
- Rappahannock Station Battlefield Park (Acc. 45052), 2009 Oct 7 (Box 5)
- Recoleta, Charlottesville (Acc. 41222), 2004 (Box 5)
- Red Gate - Greenway Rural Historic District, Clarke County (Acc. 42473), 2004 (Box 5)
- Red Hills, Albemarle County (Acc. 37305), 2000 (Box 5)
- Red Lion Tavern, Winchester (Acc. 35680), 1997 (Box 5)
- Reed Square - St. John's Church Historic District, Richmond City (Acc. 43430), 2006 (Box 5)
- Rice's Hotel - Hughlett's Tavern, Northumberland County (Acc. 39119), 2000 (Box 5)
- Richard Samuel Thomas House, Mansion on Main - Smithfield Historic District, Isle of Wight County (Acc. 45052), 2010 Jan 26 (Box 5)
- Rippon Lodge, Prince William County (Acc. 30155), 1978 (Box 5)
- Riveroak Tract - White Oak Road Battlefield (Acc. 44477), 2008 May 29 (Box 9)
- Roaring Springs, Gloucester County (Acc. 29886), 1974 (Box 5)
- Rochambeau Farm, Goochland County (Acc. 37305), 1998 (Box 5)
- Rock Castle, Goochland County (Acc. 29886), 1969 (Box 5)
- Rockwood, Orange County (Acc. 44477), 2007 Dec 28 (Box 9)
- Rockwood (A), Orange County (Acc. 44477), 2007 Dec 28 (Box 9)
- Rosewell, Gloucester County (Acc. 35680), 1997 (Box 5)
- Rural Plains, Hanover County (Acc. 37305), 1998 (Box 5)
- Sabine Hall, Richmond County (Acc. 35187), 1981; 1982 (Box 6)
- Salubria, Culpeper County (Acc. 41222), 1995 (Box 6)
- Saratoga, Clarke County (Acc. 35680), 1995 (Box 6)
- Schoolcraft House (Ida Schoolcraft House), Richmond City (Acc. 30155), 1977 (Box 6)
- Sears House, Staunton (Acc. 29886 and 30409), 1977; 1978 (Box 6)
- Seven Springs, King William County (Acc. 37305), 1999 (Box 6)
- Shack Mountain, Albemarle County (Acc. 42473), 1990 (Box 6)
- Shadwell Estate, Albemarle County (Acc. 39119), 2000 (Box 6)
- Shelburne Clebe, Loudoun County (Acc. 45157), 1989 (Box 6)
- Shelly Archaeological District - Ruggiero Tract, Gloucester County (Acc. 37305), 1998 (Box 6)
- Shelly Archaeological District - Tracts 1, 2, and 3, Gloucester County Acc. 35680), 1996 (Box 6)
- Shirley Plantation, Charles City County (Acc. 43430), 2006 (Box 6)
- Slaughter Pen Farm, Spotsylvania County (Acc. 43430), 2006 (Box 6)
- Sleepy Hollow, Rockbridge County (Acc. 45157), 1991 (Box 6)
- Smallwood House - Waterford Historic District, Loudoun County (Acc. 45157), 1990 (Box 6)
- Smith House (A.S. Smith House) - 206 W. Franklin St., Richmond City (Acc. 29886), 1977 (Box 6)
- Smith House (Jabez Smith House), Petersburg (Acc. 35680), 1997 (Box 6)
- Smith-Palmer House - 211 W. Franklin St., Richmond City (Acc. 29886), 1997 (Box 6)
- Springdale, Goochland County (Acc. 45052), 1008 Nov 26 (Box 10)
- St. John's AME Church, Norfolk (Acc. 33628), 1989 (Box 6)
- St. John's Church Historic District - 2111 and 2721 E. Broad St., Richmond City (Acc. 37305), 2000 (Box 6)
- St. John's Church Historic District - 2605 E. Franklin St., Richmond City (Acc. 37305), 2000 (Box 6)
- St. Julien, Spotsylvania County, (Acc. 41222) 2002 (Box 6)
- Stewart-Lee House, Richmond City (Acc. 39119), 2001 (Box 6)
- Stilwell Farm - Brandy Station Battlefield, Culpeper County (Acc. 45052), 2009 Nov 24 (Box 10)
- Stirling, Spotsylvania County (Acc. 45157), 1990 (Box 6)
- Stokes House - Old West End Historic District, Danville (Acc. 43473), 2005 (Box 6)
- Stratford Hall, Westmoreland County (Acc. 43430), 2006 (Box 6)
- Sunnyside, Southampton County (Acc. 42473), 2004 (Box 6)
- Thoroughgood House (Adam Thoroughgood House), Virginia Beach (Acc. 43430), 2005 (Box 6)
- Thunderbird Archaeological Site, Warren County (Acc. 33628), 1989; 1990 (Box 6)
- Tobacco Row Donation District, Richmond City (Acc. 37305), 1989 (Box 6)
- Toddsbury and Creek House Tract, Gloucester County (Acc. 29886 and 42473), 1975; 2004 (Box 6)
- Totomoi, Hanover County (Acc. 37305 and 42473), 1998; 2004 (Box 6)
- Townfield - Port Royal Historic District, Caroline County (Acc. 32920), 1986; 1987 (Box 6)
- Tuckahoe Plantation, Goochland County (Acc. 32920, 42473 and 43430), 1986; 2004; 2006 (Box 6)
- Tuckahoe Plantation, Goochland County (Acc. 44477), 2004 Dec 29 (Box 9)
- Turner House (Anthony Turner House) - St. John's Church Historic District, Richmond City (Acc. 43430), 2006 (Box 6)
- Tyro Mill, Nelson County (Acc. 44477) 2007 Dec 7 (Box 9)
- Union Station, Petersburg (Acc. 41222), 2002 (Box 7)
- Valley Pike Property - Fishers Hill Battlefield, Shenandoah County (Acc. 44477), 2008 Feb 8 (Box 9)
- Wade-McKinney House, Farmville (Acc. 45157), 1990 (Box 7)
- Waldron-Hancock House, Lynchburg (Acc. 33628), 1989 (Box 7)
- Wallace House (Thomas Wallace House), Petersburg (Acc. 35680), 1996 (Box 7)
- Wallen House (James Wallen House), Richmond City (Acc. 33628), 1988 (Box 7)
- Warren County Courthouse, Front Royal, Warren County (Acc. 45051), 2009 Aug 6 (Box 10)
- Warwick County Courthouse, Newport News (Acc. 39119), 2000 (Box 7)
- Waterford Historic District - Bank House, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1975 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Carr Property, Loudoun County (Acc. 41222), 2002 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Chamberlin Cottage, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1975 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Claggett House, Loudoun County (Acc. 35188), 1994 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Clearfield, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1976 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Country Store, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1975 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Cutter Open Space, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1976 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Donovon Field, Loudoun County (Acc. 45157), 1991 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Edwards House, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1976 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - The Forge, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1975 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Glass Shop, Loudoun County (Acc. 35187), 1986 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Graham House, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1976 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Graystone, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886 and 41222), 1974; 2002 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Griffith Ice House and Stable, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1974 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Griffith-Gover House, Loudoun County (Acc. 42473), 2004 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Hague-Hough House, Loudoun County (Acc. 35680), 1987 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Hardware Store (Rollinson's), Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1975 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Hillside, Loudoun County (Acc. 35680), 1996 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Hite-Hough House, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1975 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Hollingsworth-Lee House, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1976 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Hutchison Farm, Loudoun County (Acc. 43430), 2007 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - James House, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1976 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Janney-Coates House, Loudoun County (Acc. 42473), 2004 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Johnson House, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1976 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Lewis House, Loudoun County (Acc. 33628), 1977 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - McGavack House, Loudoun County (Acc. 33628), 1975 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Means House, Loudoun County (Acc. 35680), 1997 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Mendenhall House, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1975 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Mill End, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1976 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Moore-Bond Houses, Loudoun County (Acc. 45157), 1987 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Myers House, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1976 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Old Methodist Parsonage, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1976 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Schoolhouse, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1975 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Palmer House, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1976 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Parker-Bennett House, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1976 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Pink House, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1976 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Red Barn, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1975 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Sappington House, Loudoun County (Acc. 45157), 1990 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Schooley House, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1975 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Second Street Lots 39 and 40, Loudoun County (Acc. 32920 and 35187), 1986; 1987 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Sunnyside, Loudoun County (Acc. 45157), 1986 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Talbot Farm, Loudoun County (Acc. 43430), 2000 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Talbot House, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1975 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Tin Shop, Loudoun County (Acc. 35187), 1984 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Walker House, Loudoun County (Acc. 45157), 1986 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Waterford Farms, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1974 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Waterford Post Office/Williams Store, Loudoun County (Acc. 35187), 1985 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Weavers Cottage, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1976 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Wesley Community Church, Loudoun County (Acc. 39119), 2000 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Williams House, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1976 (Box 8)
- Waterford Historic District - Wisteria Cottage, Loudoun County (Acc. 29886), 1975 (Box 8)
- Waverly, Fauquier County (Acc. 29907), 1977 (Box 7)
- Waverly Hill, Staunton (Acc. 35680), 1994 (Box 7)
- Weisiger-Carrol House, Richmond City (Acc. 35680), 1994 (Box 7)
- Welbourne, Loudoun County (Acc. 42473), 1992; 2005 (Box 7)
- West Cote, Albemarle County (Acc. 39119), 2001 (Box 7)
- Westend, Louisa County (Acc. 29886), 1976 (Box 7)
- Western State Hospital, Staunton (Acc. 42473), 2005 (Box 7)
- Westover Plantation, Charles City County (Acc. 29886), 1974 (Box 7)
- Wheatland, Essex County (Acc. 45157), 1989 (Box 7)
- White's Mill, Washington County (Acc. 39119), 2001 (Box 7)
- Whitney Pound Tract - Brandy Station Battlefield (Acc. 44477), 2008 Dec 31 (Box 9)
- Williston, Orange County (Acc. 45157), 2007 (Box 7)
- Wilton, Middlesex County (Acc. 42473), 2005 (Box 7)
- Windsor Castle, Isle of Wight County (Acc. 43430), 2007 (Box 7)
- Windsor Castle, Isle of Wight County (Acc. 44477), 2008 July 24 (Box 9)
- Windsor Castle, Isle of Wight County (Acc. 45052), 2010 Mar 25 (Box 10)
- Windsor Shades, King William County (Acc. 44477), 2009 Jan 13 (Box 9)
- Woodbourne, Madison County (Acc. 39119), 2001 (Box 7)
- Woodlands, Albemarle County (Acc. 45157), 1989 (Box 7)
- Woodlawn, King George County (Acc. 45157), 1990 (Box 7)
- Woodrow Wilson Birthplace, Staunton (Acc. 44477), 2009 Apr 23 (Box 9)
- Woodside, Henrico County (Acc. 29886), 1970 (Box 7)